Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series B-MT, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series MT. Mel Tapley Collection
  - Mel Tapley Artwork (Box MT-12)
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      Chris Acemandese Hall (montage), Klytus Smith (photos). "Montage of Photos etc. Re Jefferson to Wade Article." Photomontage with cover leaf of ms. notes, 14" x 12.25. Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "Ouija." Pencil and ink drawing, 7" x 11.5". Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] A Better Homes for Black People Special." Pencil and ink drawing, 16" x 12". Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "Hungry? New York Amsterdam News serves News About..." Pencil and ink drawing, 16" x 11". Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      Mel Tapley. "Blizzard Conditions." Pencil and ink drawing, 17" x 14". Undated. Original artwork for editorial cartoon.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "Rocking or Swinging... Your kind of Views are in the N.Y. Amsterdam News." Velox copy of pencil drawing for subscription card, 12" x 18". Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "Balance World Views, Read Your Amsterdam News," "Recording the Heartbeat of the Black Community: New York Amsterdam News," "Rocking or Swinging... Your Kind of Views are in the N.Y. Amsterdam News." Pencil, 20" x 18.5", folded to 10.5" x 18.5". Undated. Three sketches for subscription cards.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "New York Amsterdam News has 30,000 More New Readers!" Pencil and ink drawing, 16.75" x 14". Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "Bargains that bloom in the Spring!" Pencil and ink drawing, 16.75" x 14". Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] Velox prints of approximately 5 editorial cartoons, stuck together in a bundle with paste. Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "Highest Indoor Jump." Pencil and ink drawing, 12" x 10.75". Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "Back Into Slavery." Photocopy of original artwork for a comic strip. 14 leaves, each 8.5" x 14". Undated. Housed in a mailing envelope addressed in ms. to Robert Lewis.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "Announcing Amsterdam News special Black Bicentennial Issue, to be published Feb. 1976." Pencil, 23.75" x 14.5", folded to 12" x 14.5". [Ca. 1975-1976.] Sketch for an advertisement. With three accompanying large-format photocopies of a later state of the artwork, each 24" x 18", folded to 12" x 18".
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "Disney Land." Ink drawing, 11" x 8.5". Undated. With two accompanying 11" x 8.5" photocopies of the completed cartoon.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "You Don’t Have to be a Square." Ink drawing, 5.5" x 8.5". Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "What does the Future Hold? Read the Amsterdam News." Ink drawing, 5.5" x 8.5". Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "Man! These Politicians..." Ink drawing, 11" x 8.5". Undated. Sketch for a comic strip.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "Snake Oil Salesman." Pencil and ink drawing, 11" x 8.5". Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork, ca. 1995 (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "Double Tongue Comic Present the OJ Simpson Murder Media Trial Hypocracy." Pencil sketch, 8.5" x 5.5". Undated [ca. 1995].
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "[Bald men.]" Photocopy of a sketch, 8.5" x 11". Undated. Sketch for an editorial cartoon.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "NAACP - The Key to Freedom." Pen sketch, 11" x 10.25". Undated, [ca. 1996].
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Mel Tapley.] "Sterling 662 9828." Ink drawing, 11" x 8.5". Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      Velox paste-up of an unidentified page from the Amsterdam News. 17.5" x 23", folded to 11.5" x 17.5". Undated [1988 or 1995].
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      [Unidentified artist.] "[Photocopy of a drawing]," 8.5" x 5.675". Undated. With three small accompanying enclosures: A photocopied quote from Black Elk, a small photocopied drawing, and an ms. address in Gainesville, FL.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      Materials for a velox paste-up of an unidentified page from the Amsterdam News. A bundle of approximately 8 velox prints stuck together in a bundle with paste, enclosed in a piece of blueline paper folded to 17.5" x 11". With pencil sketch and ms. notes ("About the Arts") on verso of paper. Undated.
    - Mel Tapley archive - artwork (Box MT-12)
      Advertisements for the New York Times. Original advertisements (for use in full-size paste-ups) for The New York Times. 7 ads, varying sizes. Undated.
  - Unsorted Photos
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 1)
      Rich Pipeling, Joseph Sinnott, Michael Daniel, Beverly Parker, Carnegie Hall Archives, Joseph Anello, Virginia Lee Hunter, Connie Villiers, Simon Fowler, E.J. Camp, Keith Major, Jeff Tisman, Karl Crutchfield. Also one color slide and one color laser-printed image.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 2)
      Kimberly Wright, TAR, Juan Sanchez, William Straunch, Chris Haston, Reisig & Taylor, Michael Lavine, John Tannock, Allen Morgan, Rick Day, Dorothy Low. Also 3 color slides.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 3)
      Jeff Day, B+, David Roth, Mike Jones, Susan Johann, David Lee, Jeffrey St. Mary, Joseph Mulligan, Michael Lavine, J. Katz, Zhlema Jacone, David Jensen, Bert Andrews, Carol Rosegg, Norman Seeff, Paul Jeremias, Joan Marcus, Merie W. Wallace.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 4)
      Chuck Hodes, Amy Guip, Tom Copi, Dwight Carter, Adam Newman, Bert Andrews, Christian Steiner, NYC Housing Authority Photo Unit, Martha Swope, Bill Brecht, Al Beaulieu.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 5)
      David Gahr, Marc Raboy, Andrew Oxenham, Bert Andrews, Andreas Johnsen.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 6)
      Joan Marcus/Marc Bryan-Brown, Mel Wright, Bruce W. Talamon, D. Stevens, Carl Studna, Roy DeCarava (copy photographs), Catherine Ashmore, Guy Ferrandis. Also 4 slides (one color, 3 b&w).
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 7)
      Nicola Goode, Christopher Little, Cliff Lipson, Arnold Turner, Archive Photos/G.D. Hackett, Jonathan Slaff, Dablign Harward, Malik Yusef, Rick Oliver, Scott Humbert. Also 6 color slides.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 8)
      David Corio, Sue Kwon, Martha Swope Associates/William Gibson, Mike Jones, Gary Gershoff, Mark Hanauer, Matthew Rolston, Michael Le Poer Trench/Joan Marcus, Gerald Henry, Bob Greene, Kate Garner, Michael Miller, Jeffrey Scales, Janette Beckman, Gene Martin. Also one magazine clipping.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 9)
      D. Stevens, Bruce W. Talamon, Lem Peterkin, Karl Crutchfield, Dede Smith, Michael Lavine. Also one photocopied image. One print has a single leaf of ms. notes attached with paperclip.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 10)
      Lois Greenfield, Martha Holmes, Gwendolen Cates, Richard Corman. Also one postcard.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 11)
      Harry Langdon, TAR, Steve Eichner, John Ragel, Craig T. Mathew, Frank Ochenfels, Gregory Jackson, Roger Hayden Celestin, Marc Raboy, Howard Hensel, Jim Bridges, RJ Capak. Also one laser-printed image.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 12)
      Anthony Cutajar, David Vance, Richard Felber, John Abeyta Photography, Paul Natkin, Theo Krath, Bob D'Amico, Rich Hogan, Juanita M. Cole, Jeff Bender, Michael Cooper, Catherine Ashmore, LEGO, NITRO, Daniela Federici, Michael King, Tobey, Guzman, Bob Greene.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 13)
      Dell Edwards, Jonathan Slaff, Errol Sawyer, Lin Caufield Photographers, Oliver Taylor, Ken Howard, David LeShay, Ruby Washington, Channel 21.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 14)
      Alix B. Williamson, WLIW/Channel 21, Martha Swope, Kenn Duncan, Philip Ray Studios, Paul Natkin, Wagner International Photos Inc., Collis Davis. Also typescript letters signed by Bob Ganshaw and Irene Gandy.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 15)
      Jeanette Beckman, Marc Raboy, Ken Howard, Bert Andrews.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 16)
      Jeff Katz, Sheila Turner, Jacki Sallow, Danny Clinch, D. Stevens/HBO. Also two color slides.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 17)
      Carol Rosegg/Martha Swope Associates, Jeffrey H. Scales, RJ Capak, Amy Guip, Fred W. Kelly, Martha Swope, Michael Halsband, Paul Taylor, Paul Weinberg, Chester Higgins Jr., Bill Hawthorne, Terry Arthur, Steve Prezant, Ruphin Coudyzer, TAR. Also one halftone print. One print is stapled to a 2-leaf press release.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 18)
      Peter Darley-Miller, Alan Silfen, Guy Aroch, Rick Oliver, Michael P. Smith, Jim Bridges, Tony Esparza, Claudia Thompson, Susan Ragan, Carol Friedman, James Minchin, Richard Laird, Hans Neleman, Mike Jones, Cylla Von Tiedemann, David Lee, Jeffrey H. Scales, Sue Kwon.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 19)
      Ron Campbell, Gerhard Yurkovic, Martha Swope, Nancy Miller Elliott, Nick Vaccaro, Otto M. Berk, Bob Marshall, Darlene Martin, William McMahon/Gamma Liaison, Jonathan Slaff, E.J. Camp, Danny Clinch, Roberto Koltun, Paul Warner, David Lubarsky, John Werner, Rich Lubell.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 20)
      Risasi-Zachariah Dais, Daniel Hastings, Guzman, Marty Sohl, Keith Major, Stephanie Berger. Two prints are attached to an ms. note dated 9-13-14 and two computer-printed typescript articles (by Eunice Townsend and Risasi Zachariah Dais).
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 21)
      Jeff Bender, Dennis Williford, Gustavo Ten-Hoever, B+, Paul Ryder, Jonathan Slaff, Randy Tapper, Ron Campbell, Richard Foreman, Joan Marcus. Also two computer-printed typescript "Reading the Score" columns by Raoul Abdul (4 leaves total) and two slides in a sealed envelope. Note on folder: "Mr. Tapley - From Mr. Walker."
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 22)
      Samir Id-Deen, Lem Peterkin Photo, George West Photo, Stephanie Berger Photography, Juanita M. Cole, Edward King, Karl Crutchfield, Mel Wright, Jerry Speier, Halin, Kwame Brathwaite, Bill Moore, Gregory Ross.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 23)
      Karl Crutchfield, Halin, George West, Edward Reed, Bill Moore, Thomasine Barton-Gangadean, Pictorial Enterprise, Dave Greene, Bryan Hall, Monroe S. Frederick II.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 24)
      Narman E. Harris, Karl Crutchfield, Dina Alfano, James Gilbert, Steve Azzara, Bill Moore, Pictorial Enterprise, Risasi-Zachariah Dais. Also two color slides, three photocopied images, and one autograph letter signed from Shaun Rhea.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 25)
      George West, Karl Crutchfield, Bill Moore, Risasi-Zachariah Dais, Bert Andrews, Andreas Johnsen, Laura Andrews, Chuck Pulin, Gerald Peart, Asondra Hunter, Karl Crutchfield, Austin Hansen, John Kernick, Annette Jones, Rita E. Henderson, Donovan R. Gopie, Ali Rahman.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 26)
      Allen Morgan, Bill Moore, Jack Vartoogian, Wide World Photos, Pictorial Enterprise, D. Davis, Karl Crutchfield, Klytus, Klytus Smith, Teds Photos/Ted Merriman, Garland Lee Thompson, George West, Larry Busacca, Mel Wright, James Gilbert, Jeffrey Taylor, Gerald Peart, Samir Id-Deen, Tom Zuback, Wali Amin Muhammad, Kerika Fields, Laura Andrews. Also one laser-printed image, one velox print, and autograph letter signed by Desiree Barber (attached to one print with staples), and a typescript letter signed by "Major" (paperclipped to one print).
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 27)
      Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, L. St. Clair Dummett, Carmen de Jesus, Barend van Herpe, Tajah Murdock, Hakim Mutlaq, Fred W. Kelly, Jeffrey Taylor, Marilyn Nance, Juanita M. Cole, Lecia D. Swain. One print is a Polaroid.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 28)
      Photos by Luigi, Norman Frederick, Pictorial Enterprise, Sam Siegel, Dave Greene, Anton J. Mikofsky, Amas Repertory Theatre, R. C. Learning Tree Inc., Jim Coner, Bill Price.
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 29)
      Pictorial Enterprise, Dave Greene, U.S. Army Signal Corps/Canafond, Bryan D. Hall. Also one contact sheet (25 images).
    - Unsorted Press Photos (Box MT-3, Folder 30)
      Joseph Maynard, Sherlock Robinson, Bill Moore, RJ Capak, Andreas Johnsen, Hakim Mutlaq, Morgan & Marvin Smith, Risasi-Zachariah Dais, Melba Hober, Wayne K. Garfield, Ken Smikle.
    - Unsorted Oversize Press Photos (Box MT-12)
      National Black Theater FESTAC; Toyle Anderson signed photo by Uli Rose from David Guion
  - Press Mailings
    - Abel, O'Neal L. (Box MT-4, Folder 1)
      Benny Andrews's artwork from America Series showcased at Sid Deutsch Gallery.
    - AC-BAW Center For The Arts (Box MT-4, Folder 2)
      Information from Bill Howard, letters to Jane Alexander and cultural organizations across the country.
    - Actors Producing Alliance (Box MT-4, Folder 3)
      Actors Producing Alliance presents Crossroads, three original one-act plays.
    - African Heritage Movie Network (Box MT-4, Folder 4)
      Broadcast of Purple Rain.
    - Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater (Box MT-4, Folder 5)
      1995 Season Subscription Brochure.
    - Amuauan (Box MT-4, Folder 6)
      Postcard with info on Painting-Print-Sculpture exhibition, March 20-April 4, 1982.
    - Ambassade De France, February 22, 1982. (Box MT-4, Folder 7)
      French Minister of External Relations Claude Cheysson Interview With Newsweek (International Edition).
    - The American Academy And Institute Of Arts And Letters (Box MT-4, Folder 8)
      1982 Academy Institute Awards.
    - American Ballet Theatre (Box MT-4, Folder 9)
      Three Premieres by Twyla Tharp Highlight American Ballet Theatre's May 1 Spring Gala.
    - American Broadcast Companies, Inc. (Box MT-4, Folder 10)
      WABC-TV Press Release.
    - The American Federation of Arts (Box MT-4, Folder 11)
      The American Federation of Arts appoints Serena Rattazzi as its new director.
    - The American Film Institute (Box MT-4, Folder 12)
      Poster and press release for The American Film Institute's Seminars, Workshops, Film/Lecture Series Winter/Spring 1982.
    - American Museum of Natural History (Box MT-4, Folder 13)
      Museum Programs & Exhibitions for the month of October, 1990.
    - American Theater of Harlem (Box MT-4, Folder 14)
      Detective Story by Sidney Kingsley.
    - American Youth Theatre (Box MT-4, Folder 15)
      "Cultural Expansion" (The Poets and Their Words).
    - Anichini Gallery (Box MT-4, Folder 16)
      Exhibition Shades Of Gray by Norma Nutman.
    - Annual 52nd Street Americana Festival (Box MT-4, Folder 17)
      Third Annual Duke Ellington Memorial Awards.
    - The Anthropology Museum of the People of New York (Box MT-4, Folder 18)
      Two Week Archaeological Tour.
    - The Arcenciel Opera Company Ltd. (Box MT-4, Folder 19)
      Feature on the opera "Lo Schiavo".
    - Arthur's Tavern (Box MT-4, Folder 20)
      Celebrating 1 year anniversary under new management with "A Night of Real Jazz & Blues".
    - Arts & Entertainment Network (Box MT-4, Folder 21)
      New investigative series World In Action.
    - Art Students League of New York, Inc. (Box MT-4, Folder 22)
      Booklet on lectures, exhibitions, workshops, seminars, and special events.
    - Association of Independent Video And Filmmakers, Inc. (Box MT-4, Folder 23)
      An Evening With An International Lineup Of Film And Television Makers.
    - Atlantic Records (Box MT-4, Folder 24)
      Glenn Jones "Here I Am" Live, Christmas Tree Lighting Party.
    - Atlee, Howard (Box MT-4, Folder 25)
      "NEC To Present 'Colored People's Time' By Leslie Lee at Cherry Lane", "Mayor Koch Honors Black Theatre Day At City Hall", "Negro Ensemble Company Honored By State Of New York", "New York State Celebrates Negro Ensemble Company Week", "Alan Weeks From 'Sophisticated Ladies' To Detective O.K. Kelly In 'Baker's Dozen'".
    - BANC-IV Financial Services (Box MT-4, Folder 26)
      "Dazzler" pamphlet.
    - BACA/The Brooklyn Arts Council (Box MT-4, Folder 27)
      "Seen And Unseen: A Documentary Photography Exhibition".
    - Barfield Public Relations, Inc. (Box MT-4, Folder 28)
      "The Royal League Club Of Beaufort, S.C. Donates $5000 To Historic Penn Center For Land Prevention In The Sea Islands".
    - Barnes & Noble (Box MT-4, Folder 29)
      Barnes & Noble Events, May 1995.
    - Bay Press (Box MT-4, Folder 30)
      Booklet introducing new books.
    - Beardman, John (Box MT-4, Folder 31)
      "Skin Deep: Stretching Painting".
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation (Box MT-4, Folder 32)
      Billie Holiday Theatre To Present Gala Benefit Performance Of "Lotto" At Lincoln Center.
    - Bergen Youth Orchestra (Box MT-4, Folder 33)
      The Bergen Youth Orchestra's Concert "40", under direction of Eugene Minor.
    - Berry, Sheila P. (Box MT-4, Folder 34)
      Ray Gordon Specials at LaGree Baptist Church, with The Estatistics, Edgar Kendricks, The Angelettes, LeVaughn Crosby, and Gospelettes.
    - Blackberry Productions (Box MT-4, Folder 35)
      Presenting A Spiritual Journey: Part One.
    - Blue Note (Box MT-4, Folder 36)
      The Charley Krachy Trio, Phyllis Hyman.
    - Blunt Recordings (Box MT-4, Folder 37)
      Wildlife Society. Accompanied by CD, CD-2021.
    - The Boehm Quintette, Inc. (Box MT-4, Folder 38)
      Concert at The Great Hall of Cooper Union.
    - Boneau/Bryan-Brown (Box MT-4, Folder 39)
      Madison Square Garden Presents A Christmas Carol.
    - Bonner, Beverly (Box MT-4, Folder 40)
      Beverly Bonner featured in East Henry Street.
    - Bronx Arts Ensemble (Box MT-4, Folder 41)
      Summermusic '95 presents "Ragtime Favorites".
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music (Box MT-4, Folder 42)
      Martha Clarke's Endangered Species.
    - Brooklyn Arts & Culture Association, Inc. (Box MT-4, Folder 43)
      "'Mimes And Miniatures' United Again In Baca Downtown Center Panorama".
    - Brooklyn College (Box MT-4, Folder 44)
      Honor Student Recital at Preparatory Center For The Performing Arts at Brooklyn College.
    - Brooklyn Public Library (Box MT-4, Folder 45)
      "'Talking' World Book At Brooklyn Public Library".
    - Burson-Marsteller (Box MT-4, Folder 46)
      "'Big Blue Marble' Makes TV History With Visit To People's Republic Of China".
    - Butcher, M.A. (Box MT-4, Folder 47)
      "Thou Talkin' to Me? A Cabby's Poetic License".
    - Canaan Senior Center Service (Box MT-4, Folder 48)
      Community Affairs Bulletin.
    - Capitol Records (Box MT-4, Folder 49)
      Hami, "Eddie, Gerald And Sean Levert Sing Musical Tribute To The Whispers".
    - Carlson Publishing, Inc. (Box MT-4, Folder 50)
      Black Women In America: An Historical Encyclopedia.
    - Carnegie Hall (Box MT-4, Folder 51)
      "American Symphony Orchestra Honors Leopold Stokowski's 100th Anniversary At Carnegie Hall Sunday, April 18 At 3PM".
    - Catherine Street Artist Project (Box MT-4, Folder 52)
      Harvey Wang: "Most Of The Girls Like To Dance But Only Some Of The Boys Like To: An Exhibition of Painted Photographs".
    - CBS Records (Box MT-4, Folder 53)
      Photo of group Surface recording new album 3 Deep.
    - CBS Television Network (Box MT-4, Folder 54)
      Leona Helmsley: The Queen of Mean, Anthony Zerbe, "The Road To New Orleans", Henry Fonda, Ray Bolger, "Will Martin Appointed Executive Art Director, CBS Entertainment", "Ernest Cunningham Appointed Executive Copy Director, CBS Entertainment", Tournament Players Club, "Corporate And Creative Managerial Challenges For The 1980's", "Peter Donlon Named European Operations Manager, CBS Sports, Mike Wallace.
    - Celebrate Broadway (Box MT-4, Folder 55)
      "Broadway Post Opening Dates For The Month Of March".
    - Celebrate Brooklyn (Box MT-4, Folder 56)
      Card invitation to Absolut Brooklyn Jazz concert.
    - Cema (Box MT-4, Folder 57)
      Heather B.
    - Center for Inter-American Relations (Box MT-4, Folder 58)
      "'Jazz At The Center' - Latin American And Caribbean Jazz Series To Be Held At The Center For Inter-American Relations".
    - Ceres Gallery (Box MT-4, Folder 59)
      Girlhood: A Group Art Exhibition.
    - Chappell Music Company (Box MT-4, Folder 60)
      "Chappell's Rory Bourke and Charlie Black score with multiple chart hits of 6 and 5 respectively".
    - Charka (Box MT-4, Folder 61)
      Ratula Sen.
    - Circle In The Square (Box MT-4, Folder 62)
      "Philip Bosco And Betty Miller Star in "Eminent Domain", New Play by Percy Granger."
    - Circle Repertory Company (Box MT-4, Folder 63)
      Opening performances of William Shakespeare's Richard II and the World Premiere of John Bishop's The Great Grandson Of Jedediah Kohler.
    - The City College of New York (Box MT-4, Folder 64)
      "Three Latino Voices in New York City", Yania Tierra, René Fortunato.
    - City of New York, Department of Parks And Recreation (Box MT-4, Folder 65)
      Gary Tennenbaum At The Arsenal Gallery.
    - Clark, Carlos (Box MT-4, Folder 66)
      "Touchdown -- Another Score For Singer/Actress Roslyn Burrough!!"
    - Clarke, Lesley Mitchell (Box MT-4, Folder 67)
      "Singer, Composer, Pianist Daryl Sherman Performs at "The Knickerbocker"".
    - Cohn & Wolfe (Box MT-4, Folder 68)
      Family Matters "major announcement".
    - Colden Center For The Performing Arts (Box MT-4, Folder 69)
      Betty Allen To Narrate "Babar".
    - Coleman, Eric (Box MT-4, Folder 70)
      Eric Coleman stars in Shakespeare's Othello.
    - Columbia Records (Box MT-4, Folder 71)
      Mariah Carey Daydream.
    - Columbia University (Box MT-4, Folder 72)
      An Evening of French Songs with French singer Eric Vincent.
    - Composers' Forum, Inc. (Box MT-4, Folder 73)
      "New Music" advertisements.
    - Concert Royal (Box MT-4, Folder 74)
      "Opera Ballet by Jean-Philippe Rameau: New York Original Instrument Premiere of the "Prologue" and "Les Incas De Perou" from Les Indes Galantes".
    - Congress of the United States (Box MT-4, Folder 75)
      Nonprofit Mail Rate Increase, "Chisholm Cautions Against 'Tinkering' With Head Start".
    - Cooper Union (Box MT-4, Folder 76)
      1996 Cooper Union Alumni Directory.
    - Corporation for Public Broadcasting (Box MT-4, Folder 77)
      CPB Report, September 10 1990.
    - Cotter, Jill (Box MT-4, Folder 78)
      Sonja Sohn: Finger in the Socket Salon.
    - Creative Arts Workshops for Homeless Children (Box MT-4, Folder 79)
      President Ruth Messinger and Councilwoman Carolyn Maloney to speak at candlelight vigil in recognition of the children who died this year in crack-related violence.
    - Cromarty & Co. (Box MT-4, Folder 80)
      "Bugs Bunny Celebrates His 50th Birthday On Broadway With Rarely Seen Vintage Cartoons Set To Classical Music Performed Live Beginning On Wednesday, October 3rd At The Gershwin Theater".
    - Crossroads Theatre Company (Box MT-4, Folder 81)
      A Lovesong For Miss Lydia.
    - The Curtis Institute Of Music (Box MT-4, Folder 82)